http://www.cookebrothers.co.uk/privacy-policy

COVID-19 STATUS
IMPORTANT INFORMATION FROM COOKE BROTHERS. FIND OUT MORE
Close
Welcome to the Cooke Brothers Website. This site uses cookies, please read our policy.
Close
Products
Architectural Hinges
Concealed BearingCover Plate HingesDual BearingGlass DoorLoadmasterReduced-LigaturePlain KnuckleShrouded BearingSlimlineWashered KnuckleCompliance & GradingCorrosion ResistanceHinge ClassificationInstallation InformationOverview
Continuous Hinges
OverviewArchitecturalLight DutyMedium DutyHeavy DutyFire Door KitInstallation Infomation
PIVOTA Concealed Hinges
OverviewPIVOTA Hinges
Shelf Support Systems
OverviewFlat Shelf SupportM Section Shelf SupportRaised Shelf SupportU Section Shelf SupportStuds & AccessoriesInstallation Information
Cabinet Fittings
OverviewDecorative HingesExtruded HingesGlass PlateLift-off HingesScreen Hinges
Architectural Hardware
OverviewFlush BoltsFlush PullsInset HandlesLetter Plates & TidiesPush PlatesVision Panels - CircularVision Panels - Rectangular Vision Panels - Square
Anti-Barricade Door Systems
Overview
Bespoke Manufacturing
Services
ManufacturingProduct TestingResearch & DevelopmentWarehousing & DespatchCut to Length ServiceNormid SimplifilePhoenix Balustrading
About
CertificationsCorporate ResponsibilityCustomer InitiativesCustomer ServicesOur Quality
Resources
NewsBlogFAQsDocumentsTechnicalLinks
How to Buy
Delivery InformationFind a Stockist Returns Policy
Contact
Staff Contacts
Special Offers
Return to Content
Home/ Privacy Policy
Privacy Policy
This privacy policy sets out how Cooke Brothers uses and protects any information that you provide when you use this website.
Cooke Brothers is committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. Should we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using this website, it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement.
Data Collection
We may collect personal information that you provide via forms on this website for example when you fill out our enquiry form.
We require this information solely for the purpose of servicing your requests and providing a better service to you, particularly for the following reasons:
To help us improve the services we provide
To help you make informed decisions when purchasing our products
From time to time send promotional emails about new products, special offers or other information which we think you may find interesting, only with your explicit acceptance.
We will not sell, distribute or lease your personal information to third parties unless we have your permission or are required by law to do so. If you have submitted information to us and wish to have them removed from our internal records, please email us privacy@cookebrothers.co.uk.
Cookies
To view information about how Cooke Brothers use Cookies, please review our Cookie Policy.
Other Websites
Cooke Brothers may provide a number of links to third party sites. Cooke Brothers assumes no responsibility for the information practices of sites a visitor is able to access through ours, and we encourage visitors to review each site's privacy policy before disclosing any personally details.
Disclaimer
The content provided on this site is on ‘as is’ and ‘as available’ basis and Cooke Brothers assume no responsibility for its accuracy or reliability. All content on this site is for general information purposes only, and although we try to keep this content up-to-date and correct, we make not warranties, expresses or implied about the accuracy, reliability, suitability or availability with respect to the website, its content or related graphics it contains for any purpose. Any reliance you place on such information is therefore strictly at your own risk.In no event will we be liable for any loss or damage including without limitation, indirect or consequential loss or damage, or any loss or damage whatsoever arising from loss of data or profits arising out of, or in connection with, the use of this website.This policy is subject to change. You should check this page from time to time to ensure that you are happy with any changes before disclosing any information to us.
Order Summary
There are no products in your order.
Send to friend
Forgotten your password?
Login
New Customers
Don't have a Cooke Brothers Account? Create an account now.
Register
